Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983 UE.4.1.5
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 5, 1.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour, September 9, 1943; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 20, 1943; 19.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, November 9, 1943; 20.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Constitutions, Local 516, and Charters, January 25, 1944; 1.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, January 26, 1944; 2.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Mailing List, February 8, 1944; 3.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and Constitution with Lists, March 7, 1944; 4.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Local 515 Finances, April 3, 1944; 5.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita and Canadian Congress of Labour, April 6, 1944; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Dues and Local 504, April 7, 1944; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding GE Publicity, May 9, 1944; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding GE and Publicity, July 12, 1944; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita and CCL, July 13, 1944; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 18, 1944; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Union Shop, July 19, 1944; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 7, 1944; 13.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 15, 1944; 14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Union Security, August 16, 1944; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 5, 1944; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding CCL, October 3, 1944; 17.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 4, 1944; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 17, 1944; 19.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Dues and Local 527, October 26, 1944; 20.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, November 2, 1944; 21.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding CCL, November 10, 1944; 22.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, November 17, 1944; 23.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Finances, December 4, 1944; 1.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, December 20, 1944; 2.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Local 527 Dues, January 25, 1945; 3.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita and Local 523, February 1, 1945; 4.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 7, 1945; 5.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 4, 1945; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 16, 1945; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding UE Constitutions and Per Capita, May 2, 1945; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Local 510 and Per Capita, May 7, 1945; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 8, 1945; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 5, 1945; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 18, 1945; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 17, 1945; 13-14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Local 513 Disbanding, October 5, 1945; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 4, 1946; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding CCL, June 12, 1946; 17.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 6, 1946; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding General Executive Board, August 27, 1946; 19.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 18, 1946; 20.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 31, 1946; 21.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding General Executive Board, November 7, 1947; 22.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, December 2, 1947; 23.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Finances, March 2, 1948; 1.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 17, 1948; 2.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 5, 1948; 3.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 16, 1948; 4.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 19, 1948; 5.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 1, 1948; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 4, 1948; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 15, 1948; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 8, 1948; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 21, 1948; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 3, 1948; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 17, 1948; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 21, 1948; 13.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Local 512 and Supplies, October 8, 1948; 14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour, April 27, 1949; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, May 4, 1949; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 5, 1949; 17.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 2, 1949; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 17, 1949; 19.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 5, 1949; 20.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 18, 1949; 21.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 2, 1949; 22.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 18, 1949; 23.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding 1949 UE Convention, August 30, 1949; 24.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 7, 1949; 25.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 16, 1949; 26.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Finances, October 2, 1949; 1.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and Constitution, October 4, 1949; 2.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 21, 1949; 3.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 28, 1949; 4.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 6, 1950; 5.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 15, 1950; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 18, 1950; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 28, 1950; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Charters for Locals 517 and 532, October 5, 1950; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 19, 1950; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, January 17, 1951; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 27, 1951; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 21, 1951; 13.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 22, 1951; 14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 4, 1951; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 16, 1951; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 17, 1951; 17.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 3, 1951; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 18, 1951; 19.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Dues Check-off, May 31, 1951; 20.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 25, 1951; 21.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 5, 1951; 22.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 15, 1951; 23.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 5, 1951; 24.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Finances, August 7, 1951; 1.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 20, 1951; 2.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 21, 1951; 3.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 24, 1951; 4.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 5, 1951; 5.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, November 8, 1951; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and Local 504, November 23, 1951; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, December 7, 1951; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, January 8, 1952; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, January 29, 1952; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 5, 1952; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals, February 18, 1952; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 21, 1952; 13.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 4, 1952; 14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 19, 1952; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 4, 1952; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 18, 1952; 17.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 7, 1952; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 10, 1952; 19.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 20, 1952; 20.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 2, 1952; 21.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, July 24, 1952; 22.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, August 1, 1952; 23.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 8, 1952; 24.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 8, 1952; 25.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Finances, November 6, 1952; 1.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, December 3, 1952; 2.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, January 13, 1953; 3.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita and District 5 Locals, January 20, 1953; 4.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, February 17, 1953; 5.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, February 24, 1953; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 4, 1953; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita and Local 514, April 3, 1953; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, April 7, 1953; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 4, 1953; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 3, 1953; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, July 9, 1953; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, September 17, 1953; 13.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, October 6, 1953; 14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals, November 18, 1953; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals, May 11, 1954; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals, May 18, 1954; 17.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, January 21, 1955; 18.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals, March 21, 1955; 19.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1951 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Albert Fitzgerald to George Harris Regarding District 5 Locals, October 7, 1947; 1.
    - A.M. Gibson to Harris Regarding Supplies, October 24, 1944; 2.
    - L. Harris to Harris Regarding Strikes and Philco Toronto, August 21, 1947; 3.
    - Leo Jandreau to Harris Regarding Grievances, December 27, 1943; 4.
    - Ray Klausner to Harris Regarding Address List, February 3, 1948; 5.
    - Peter Mantler to Harris Regarding Local 529 and Factionalism, September 9, 1948; 6.
    - James Matles to Harris Regarding Local 513 and Supplies with August 28, 1941, Jack Shaw Letter to Matles, August 29, 1941; 7.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding GE, March 5, 1943; 8.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding Finances and Aluminum Workers, May 26, 1943; 9.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding Labor Education, July 14, 1943; 10.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding Amalgamated Electric Organization, July 22, 1943; 11.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding Canada Wire & Cable Organization, December 19, 1945; 12.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, Inter-union Rivalry, Contracts, and GE, December 15, 1950; 13.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 15, 1950; 14.
    - Matles to Harris Regarding Proctor Electric and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 14, 1951; 15.
    - Emma Meagher to Harris Regarding 1951 UE Convention, September 18, 1951; 16.
    - Ed Matthews to Harris Regarding Strike, Incentive, and War Labor Board, March 4, 1944; 17.
    - Matthews to Harris Regarding Westinghouse Strike, July 25, 1946; 18.
    - Don Pinkston to Harris Regarding Publicity, January 10, 1946; 19.
    - David Ratner to Harris Regarding U.S. Label, February 9, 1949; 20.
    - Nat Spero to Harris Regarding Strikes, June 20, 1951; 21.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - George Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding GE Toronto Organization, August 12, 1941; 1.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding GE Collective Bargaining, August 12, 1941; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding GE Toronto Organization, August 14, 1941; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Local 514 Address Change, September 19, 1941; 4.
    - Harris to All UE Locals Regarding Membership, October 15, 1941; 5.
    - Harris to Local Financial Secretaries Regarding Finances, October 15, 1941; 6.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Coulter Copper Collective Bargaining, October 27, 1941; 7.
    - Harris to Tom Wright Regarding Internment, November 30, 1941; 8.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Coulter Copper Contract and Local 514, December 8, 1941; 9.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 10, 1941; 10.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 20, 1942; 11.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Customs, February 23, 1943; 12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances and Small Arms Organization, May 18, 1942; 13.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding WWII, June 1, 1942; 14.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Taylor Electric Organization, July 29, 1942; 15.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 17, 1942; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding District 5 Locals and Contracts, January 8, 1943; 17.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Ontario Organization and Finances, January 26, 1943; 18.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding GE Peterboro Organization, January 30, 1943; 19.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Local 518 Finances, February 16, 1942; 20.
    - Harris to Martles Regarding Organization and GE Peterboro, February 23, 1943; 21.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - George Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 522 Officers, June 7, 1943; 1.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding UE News, June 22, 1943; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour, June 22, 1943; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding CCL and Per Capita with Delegate List, June 23, 1943; 4.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Labor Education and No-Strike Pledge, July 5, 1943; 5.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Mailing List, July 14, 1943; 6.
    - Harris to Staff Regarding War Labor Board and Local 523, October 8, 1943; 7.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding CCL and Per Capita, December 14, 1943; 8.
    - Harris to Leo Jandreau Regarding GE Grievances, December 18, 1943; 9.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, January 15, 1944; 10.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Constitution and Dues, January 21, 1944; 11.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Organization, February 3, 1944; 12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances and Supplies, February 29, 1944; 13.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances and Constitution, March 4, 1944; 14.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Incentive, March 8, 1944; 15.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Local 515 Finances, March 31, 1944; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, April 1, 1944; 17.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Dues, April 1, 1944; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding CCL and Per Capita, April 11, 1944; 19.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Hamilton Organization and White Collar Worker Organization at Westinghouse Toronto, April 20, 1944; 20.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Organization and Local 513, April 20, 1944; 21.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - George Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and Per Capita, May 5, 1944; 1.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 7, 1944; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Union Security, July 7, 1944; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, July 10, 1944; 4.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 11, 1944; 5.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, August 2, 1944; 6.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 24, 1944; 7.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding CCL and Per Capita, September 5, 1944; 8.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding GE Peterboro Organization and Factionalism, October 4, 1944; 9.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, October 6, 1944; 10.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 31, 1944; 11.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Address Change, November 8, 1944; 12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, January 10, 1945; 13.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, Unemployment, and Organization, February 1, 1945; 14.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Collective Bargaining and Union Security, February 15, 1945; 15.
    - Harris to Ray Klausner Regarding Locals 513 and 518, April 3, 1945; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Local 513 and Disbanding, May 5, 1945; 17.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances and Literature, April 6, 1945; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, Supplies, and Organization, April 28, 1945; 19.
    - Harris to Klausner Regarding Finances, Supplies, and Organization, April 28, 1945; 20.
    - Harris to Klausner Regarding Per Capita and CCL with List, May 11, 1945; 21.
    - Harris to Klausner Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 524 and 527 and Locals 515 and 520, June 28, 1945; 22.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Local 507 Organization, July 14, 1945; 23.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - George Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and Per Capita with List, August 29, 1945; 1.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Local 513 Disbanding, October 1, 1945; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Montreal Organization, November 14, 1945; 3.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Mailing List, November 15, 1945; 4.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 16, 1945; 5.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Mailing List, November 15, 1945; 6.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding GE, January 3, 1946; 7.
    - Harris to Ray Klausner Regarding Hotel Reservations, January 11, 1946; 8.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Disbanding of Locals 514 and 521, January 25, 1946; 9.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Ford Factionalism Strike, CCL, and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry with February 12, 1946, C.S. Jackson Letter to A.R. Mosher, February 26, 1946; 10.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, May 17, 1946; 11.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 13, 1946; 12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 17, 1946; 13.
    - Harris to UE Regarding USWA Inter-union Rivalry with June 18, 1946, Harris Letter to Sally Brass Employees, and June 14, 1946, Harris Letter to C.H. Millard, June 19, 1946; 14.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, June 19, 1946; 15.
    - Harris to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Strike, July 6, 1946; 16.
    - Harris to Peter Abbondi Regarding Westinghouse Strike, July 10, 1946; 17.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - George Harris to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Strike, July 19, 1946; 1.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, August 17, 1946; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and Per Capita with Per Capita List, December 11, 1946; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry and Sully Brass, December 11, 1946; 4.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 14, 1946; 5.
    - Harris to Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, December 23, 1946; 6.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances with Finances, February 6, 1947; 7.
    - Harris to District Council Delegates Regarding District 5 Constitutions, February 10, 1947; 8.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, February 27, 1947; 9.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 203, March 5, 1947; 10.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, March 10, 1947; 11.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, May 17, 1947; 12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, May 22, 1947; 13.
    - Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 27, 1947; 14.
    - Harris to District Council Delegates Regarding CCL, October 23, 1947; 15.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Women's Auxiliary and Local 525, November 17, 1947; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 518, November 22, 1947; 17.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 25, 1947; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 1, 1947; 19.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Political Action, January 13, 1948; 20.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, February 9, 1948; 21.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, February 10, 1948; 22.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - George Harris to Selma Tauber Regarding Staff Members, February 18, 1948; 1.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies and Local 535, July 9, 1948; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 23, 1948; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 24, 1948; 4.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, Strikes, and Seamen, August 4, 1948; 5.
    - Harris to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Organization and White Collar Workers, November 25, 1948; 6.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 19, 1949; 7.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, March 10, 1949; 8.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 15, 1949; 9.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Customs, February 3, 1949; 10.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, April 21, 1949; 11.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour, April 30, 1949; 12.
    - Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Strikes and Local 531, August 24, 1949; 13.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding 1949 UE Convention, August 24, 1949; 14.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Remmington Rand Hamilton and Inter-union Rivalry, November 2, 1949; 15.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Per Capita, January 27, 1950; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 4, 1950; 17.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with Resolutions, July 17, 1950; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 3, 1950; 19.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Local 518, October 16, 1950; 20.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding IUE, December 12, 1950; 21.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding IUE and Inter-union Rivalry, February 8, 1951; 22.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 10, 1951; 23.
  - District 5 George Harris Outgoing Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - George Harris to Lillian Rosenberg Regarding Dominion Rope Belleville Lock Strike, March 7, 1951; 1.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 8, 1951; 2.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding GE Collective Bargaining, Per Capita, IUE Inter-union Rivalry, Dominon Rope and Belleville Lock Strikes, and Organization, March 28, 1951; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 7, 1951; 4.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding High Treason, June 11, 1951; 5.
    - Harris to Nat Spero Regarding Dominon Wire and Belleville Lock Strikes and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, June 22, 1951; 6.
    - Harris to David Ratner Regarding 1951 UE Convention, July 3, 1951; 7.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, September 28, 1951; 8.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund, November 20, 1951; 9.